# **Alissa Champigny**

Full Stack Web Developer

Kingston, NH (603) 793-2449 achampigny4@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

**Full Stack Web Developer** who graduated from UNH's coding bootcamp December 2020. Known for excellent people skills and being a supportive team member that is effective in developing user-friendly applications. **Prior experience** includes 11 years in the medical field.

### **PROJECTS**

## **Job Trackr** — Project Manager and Full Stack Developer

https://whispering-woodland-82554.herokuapp.com/ https://github.com/achampigny4/Job-Trackr

A remote job search application that allows the user to track each step of the application process all in one location. This app resolves the need for multiple logins on multiple sites to find the status of their job application.

Technologies: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Material–UI, React.js, Remotive API, Node.js, Axios, Express.js, Concurrently, Passport.js, Bcrypt.js, MySQL, Sequelize, Heroku, Dotenv, ESLint, nodemon

## **Adults Only Petfinder** — Front End Developer

https://github.com/achampigny4/adults-pet-finder https://hilbug.github.io/adults-pet-finder/

Comedic browser-based application in which a user over 18 years old can be matched with a randomized pet profile. Underage users are provided with resources to learn about pet adoption.

Technologies: Materialize css framework, JQuery, Animate.css, Scrollreveal.js, Font Awesome, Google Fonts, Embed Responsively.

## We Workout App — Full Stack Developer

https://github.com/RisleyDwayne/we-workout https://weworkoutapp.herokuapp.com/

Mobile friendly application which allows users who infrequently workout to easily exercise at home. We Workout's database provides premade workouts, exercise explanations and the ability to create personalized workouts.

Technologies: Sequelize, Passport, MySQL, Node.js, Express, Express-Handlebars, ESLint, jQuery, Heroku, CSS, HTML, Bootstrap, Trello, Balsamiq.

#### **CONNECT**

www.linkedin.com/in/alissa-champigny
https://github.com/achampigny4
https://achampigny4.github.io/AlissaC-

https://achampigny4.github.io/AlissaC-ResponsivePortfolio/

#### **PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES**

HTML, CSS, Javascript.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

React, Jquery, responsive design, Bootstrap, Materialize, Material UI, Node.js, OOP, SQL, NoSQL, MongoDB, Sequelize, AJAX, APIs, Express.js, Handlebars.js, Github, Heidi SQL, Heroku, analytical skills, search engine optimization, testing and debugging.

#### **INTERPERSONAL SKILLS**

- Ambitious
- Organized
- Dedicated

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Coding Bootcamp**, UNH — *Certificate*

DECEMBER 2020

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

## **CT Technologist**, ARRT — Certificate

**NOVEMBER 2016** 

# Radiologic Technologist, NHTI — Associates Degree

MAY 2013

## **Licensed Nursing Assistant**, SST — Certificate

**JUNE 2009** 

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Exeter Hospital**, Exeter, NH — Radiologic Technologist

FEBRUARY 2013 - CURRENT

- Provided an interventional spine doctor with radiographic imaging during procedures.
- Passed the national registry(ARRT) and became a radiologic technologist.
- Began employment as a student radiologic technologist.

## **ConvenientMD**, Portsmouth, NH — *Radiologic Technologist*

JULY 2016 - CURRENT

- Clinical preceptor for new clinical staff.
- Created useful forms for emergent patients and lab reference guides.
- Performed basic nursing duties such as triage, obtain vitals signs, administer point of care testing.

# **Frisbie Memorial Hospital,** Rochester, NH — *Multimodality Technologist*

MARCH 2014 - NOVEMBER 2016

- Passed national CT technologist national registry.
- Administered oral and IV contrast per radiologist protocol.
- Began as a radiologic technologist and completed CT training.